首先咱们来介绍一下Claude Opus 4.6
First, let’s introduce Claude Opus 4.6
这款模型
This model
依然提供了
Still provided
100万TOKEN的上下文窗口
Context window of 1 million TOKEN
毋庸置疑
Undoubtedly
在各大基准测试的得分上
Scores on major benchmark tests
相较于过去的模型
Compared to past models
它总是最好的
it's always the best
从定价上来看
From the perspective of pricing
4.6依然使用了同样的定价
4.6 still uses the same pricing
每百万输入输出TOKEN的价格
Price of input and output TOKEN per million
分别是5美元和25美元
They are $5 and $25 respectively.
我想大家应该不常会用API
I think you don’t often use APIs.
直接来集成到比如像Claude
Directly integrate into, for example, Claude
Code等应用中
Code and other applications
更多的呢
More
还是用的订阅
Still use subscription
不过价格没有变
But the price hasn’t changed
供大家参考
For your reference
Opus 4.6模型在任务执行中
Opus 4.6 model in action
通常会进行深度的思考
Usually think deeply
谨慎的推理
careful reasoning
那么在一些任务的执行上
Then in the execution of some tasks
如果大家发觉
If everyone finds out
模型过度的进行了思考呢
Is the model overthinking?
可以通过参数effort来调整
It can be adjusted through the parameter effort
现在来到OpenAI这一侧
Now coming to the OpenAI side
新模型GPT-5.3-Codex
New model GPT-5.3-Codex
这是一款号称最强的编程模型
This is a programming model known as the strongest
同样的相较于过去的模型呢
Same thing compared to past models
它在各类测试的评分上
It scores on various tests
都表现得非常突出
All performed very prominently
目前发布的模型呢
What about the models currently released?
已经不太会跟其他厂商的模型
I am no longer able to compare with models from other manufacturers.
进行直接对比
Make a direct comparison
我们从这些基准测试的数据图表上
From the data charts of these benchmarks, we
能看到主要对比的还是自家的模型
You can see that the main comparison is still with our own model.
根据我目前对于这篇文章的扫描呢
According to my current scan of this article
并没有看到它明确的介绍
I didn’t see it clearly introduced
它的上下文窗口的长度
the length of its context window
如果大家知道的
If everyone knows
也欢迎在评论区给我留言
You are also welcome to leave me a message in the comment area
目前GPT-5.3-Codex已经可以在Codex命令行
Currently, GPT-5.3-Codex can be used on the Codex command line.
或Codex应用中使用
Or used in Codex application
我们只需要更新对应的应用程序
We just need to update the corresponding application
就可以使用到这款最新的模型了
You can use this latest model